When looking at your new VPC,
在查看您的新 VPC时
take note of all the things that are required to create a useful VPC.
请注意创建有用的 VPC 所需的所有内容
You need the VPC itself, a routing table,
您需要 VPC 本身 一个路由表
a subnet, and if you want to connect externally, an Internet gateway.
子网 如果要在外部连接 则是因特网网关
You also need all of these things connected together in the correct way.
您还需要所有这些东西以正确的方式连接在一起
Let's look through the things that have been created,
让我们看看那些创造的东西
and how they relate to each other.
以及它们之间的关系
Looking at the newly created VPC,
查看新创建的 VPC
we can see a few things about it.
我们可以看到一些关于它的东西
In particular, make note of the CIDR address that was picked while we created the VPC,
特别是 请记下我们在创建 VPC时提取的 CIDR 地址
in this case, 10.0.0.0/16.
在本案中  10.0.0.0/16.
Next, we'll take a look at the subnet.
接下来 我们就来看看子网
When we look at our subnet list,
当我们看我们的子网列表时
we see all the subnets for all of the VPCs that we have.
我们可以看到所有我们拥有的所有 VPC 的子网
We want to filter this by our newly created VPC.
我们希望通过我们新建的 VPC进行过滤
As we can see, we have one subnet created as part of this VPC.
我们可以看到 我们有一个子网作为 VPC的一部分创建
Now that we're looking at the subnet,
现在我们正在看这个子网
we can also look at the route table.
我们也可以看看路线表
Here we can see that both the VPC network address,
在这里我们可以看到 VPC 网络地址
10.0.0/16 is in the route table,
10.0.0/ 10.0.0/ 16 在路线表中
as well as another entry,
还有另一个入口
the 0.0.0.0/0 entry is really what's called a default route.
0.0.0.0/0 的条目就是所谓的默认路由
So anything that doesn't match the first role,
任何与第一个角色不匹配的东西
goes to this route entry and
转至该路由条目并
the target for that is the Internet gateway that was created.
目标是创建的因特网网关
From here, we can go and look at our Internet gateway.
从这里 我们可以去看看我们的互联网网关
As we can see, the Internet gateway is attached to our newly created VPC.
我们可以看到 因特网网关连接到我们新创建的 VPC
All of these elements connected together,
所有这些元素连接在一起
form a VPC that is actually useful to us where we can put instances in this subnet.
形成一个 VPC  它实际上对我们有用 我们可以在这个子网中放置实例
They will then use the associated route table,
然后他们将使用关联的路由表
which routes traffic through the Internet gateway,
通过互联网网关传递流量
and thus makes us a publicly accessible subnet within our new VPC.
从而使我们成为新的 VPC中可公开访问的子网